(school bell rings)
Peter Parker: I can't believe this happened
MJ: Peter, everything's gonna be okay
Peter Parker: No, my identity is exposed. Everyone knows who I am
Ned: Maybe Doctor Strange can help us
Peter Parker: We have to go to him. There's no other way
(portal opening sound)
Doctor Strange: Peter, this spell is very dangerous
Peter Parker: Please, I just want everyone to forget I'm Spider-Man
Doctor Strange: Okay, but anything you want to say?
Peter Parker: No, just that...
Doctor Strange: Too late! The spell is out of control
(explosion and blue light)
Ned: Oh my god! What just happened?
Doctor Strange: Portals to other worlds have opened
(heavy footsteps sound)
Doc Ock: Well, who are we up against?
Peter Parker: Who are you?
Doc Ock: Otto Octavius. They call me Doctor Octopus
(Green Goblin appears)
Green Goblin: Looks like we're having a party!
Peel: Am I dreaming?
Ned: If it's a dream, I've been asleep for a long time!
(Sandman sound)
Electro: Finally, a place where everyone knows who I am
Peter Parker: I have to stop these guys
Doctor Strange: No Peter, these hunters are after you
Peter Parker: It's my fault. I have to fix it
(punch and explosion sound)
Doc Ock: See? Your world is no different
(another Spider-Man sound)
Spider-Man 2: Hey, don't think you're alone!
Peter Parker: You... you're me too?
Spider-Man 2: Kind of. Long story
(Spider-Man 3 sound)
Spider-Man 3: Looks like you need some help, guys